<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ch 2 Hugo Content Structure on Hugo for Fortinet TECWorkshops</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo.html</link><description>Recent content in Ch 2 Hugo Content Structure on Hugo for Fortinet TECWorkshops</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Task 1 - Chapter Directory Structure</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/2_task1.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/2_task1.html</guid><description>Create a Folder structure correlating to the major topics/sections of the demonstration Browse to the content directory within your TECWorkshop repo (Locally on your machine) The Left Hand navigation menu is driven by the folder structure you create Chapters are ordered according to the number prefix on the folder Folder Naming doesn&amp;rsquo;t appear on the published site, it only helps the content creator organize the chapters &amp;amp; remember what&amp;rsquo;s in each Chapter Within each folder there is an _index.</description></item><item><title>Task 2 - Create/Modify MD pages</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/3_task2.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/3_task2.html</guid><description>Create or copy Markdown pages for each task within the chapter Each Chapter can have 1 or more tasks which should be completed by the participants Naming of the task Markdown pages doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, and is only used to aid the content author in organizing the content. Info Note that the filename doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter other than to help organize content. The Title and Weight dictate the leftnav visual and ordering of the pages.</description></item><item><title>Task 3 - Adjust config.toml site settings</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/4_task3.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/4_task3.html</guid><description>Adjust the Site&amp;rsquo;s Frontmatter in config.toml file Note Config.toml must be modified for each new repo as it controls overall parameters for the site Open the config.toml file under the repo root to change a few parameters of the site Edit the baseUrl parameter to match the GitHub Page for your site (it will match your TECWorkshop reop name) Edit the themeVariant parameter depending on the type of TEC Content you&amp;rsquo;re using Info Currently available themeVariants are:</description></item><item><title>Task 4 - image storage</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/images.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo/images.html</guid><description>Image Storage Option 1: use externally fully qualified absolutely path (this can be a pain) Option 2: if you have a directory with all your images&amp;hellip;. put it in &amp;ldquo;/content/images&amp;rdquo; MD usage(from a chapter page in &amp;ldquo;content/chapter01&amp;rdquo;) ![Magic](../images/magic.gif) Option 3: I find it easier to organize images with the pages they go with (this is how the template repo is setup put images in the chapter directory e.g. images in &amp;ldquo;/content/chapter1/&amp;rdquo; MD Usage: !</description></item></channel></rss>