<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fortinet TECWorkshop Template - MVP1 on Hugo for Fortinet TECWorkshops</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Fortinet TECWorkshop Template - MVP1 on Hugo for Fortinet TECWorkshops</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ch 1 Getting Started with Repos, Containers, and Hugo</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted.html</guid><description>Setting up your Hugo environment (15 min) Prereqs Docker - older installs won&amp;rsquo;t work, so if you need to upgrade/reinstall, follow this procedure GitHub keys Follow the instructions here to generate a new SSH key pair Warning DO NOT USE A PASSPHRASE when you create the keys Once created follow these directions to add the newly created Key to your GitHub account. What is Hugo and how easy can this be?</description></item><item><title>Ch 2 Hugo Content Structure</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/02hugo.html</guid><description>Learn to organize and create content in Hugo- estimated duration 20min You now have a container running hugo webserver and tracking changes to the /content directory in your repo.
Create your TecWorkshop Guide including Chapers and tasks. You can use your favorite editor/IDE to create the markdown pages Depending on several factors, you may or may not see LIVE changes to the http://localhost:1313/UserRepo page If you&amp;rsquo;re not seeing live changes&amp;hellip; re-run hugo server command on container (ctrl+C to end the running hugo process on container CLI) Note You will ultimately need to make a minor change to the config.</description></item><item><title>Ch 3 - Hugo Publish</title><link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/03chapter3.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/03chapter3.html</guid><description>Publish your content to GitHub pages via a GitHub action Now that you have your content first draft, push your repo to github, there&amp;rsquo;s already a GitHub action to automatically publish your content anytime you upload to the repo
Click the right arrow to go through each step individually</description></item></channel></rss>